<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SiddharthVipul</title>
    <link>https://vipul.dev/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SiddharthVipul</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vipul.dev/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intellectual Curiosity curbs</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2021/intellectual_curiosity_intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2021/intellectual_curiosity_intro/</guid>
      <description>WTF is Intellectual Curiosity </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSDEM Call for Proposal</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2020/fosdem_cfp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2020/fosdem_cfp/</guid>
      <description>We are excited to announce that the call for proposals is now open for the Distribution devroom at the upcoming FOSDEM 2021, to be hosted virtually on February 6th 2021.
As more and more workloads are being considered for containerization in the future and are finally landing in virtualized environments today, distributions remain a critical success factor and are more important than ever. Containers, like virtual machines, are not magical and rely on piles of software being assembled in a way that is repeatable, reliable, and functional.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimental September</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2020/experimental_september/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2020/experimental_september/</guid>
      <description>Experimental September For a long time now I have been feeling unproductive. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I think I don&amp;rsquo;t work, just that at the end of the day/week/month, I am not happy with the amount of time I spent in front of Computer vs the amount of tangible work that comes out of it. A few days ago, Sarah Finn (CPE agile coach) reached out to me to discuss the experimental September where I was to decide 8 hours time that suits me the best and close the laptop once that time gets over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My work-from-home setup</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2020/my_wfh_setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2020/my_wfh_setup/</guid>
      <description>Before reading ahead, please remember 2 things
 Being a remote employee, this is my permanent setup. When pandemic is over, I would still be working from home. I have been doing things around my setup for almost 2 years now. I didn&amp;rsquo;t buy all these things at once and it&amp;rsquo;s still far from over.  Whenever we start investing in things/gadjets, after a point (the law of) diminishing returns hits (used to refer to a point at which the level of profits or benefits gained is less than the amount of money or energy invested).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating jobs to new OCP4 cluster</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2020/ocp-migration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2020/ocp-migration/</guid>
      <description>Action If you are currently using apps.ci.centos.org (OCP 3.6) or have a job running in ci.centos.org, please contact us so that we can create a namespace for you in the new OCP 4.4 cluster for you to start migrating your jobs.
If your own a namespace on apps.ci.centos.org There shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a lot of changes for you as you already have a workflow known to openshift and you have configured your jobs once.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flock to Fedora 2019</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2019/flock_to_fedora_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2019/flock_to_fedora_2019/</guid>
      <description>Context Last year I attended Flock to Fedora for the First time and it was one of the best events I had ever been to. After attending DevConfs, FOSDEM etc. Flock is still my favorite event to attend. Fedora 2019 was no less of an experience.
Flock to Fedora is an annual conference for Fedora contributors. Flock follows the tradition to organize the event at a different location every year. This year was no different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevConf India 2019</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2019/devconf_india_2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2019/devconf_india_2019/</guid>
      <description>Context DevConf.IN is the annual developer&amp;rsquo;s conference organised by Red Hat, India. The conference provides a platform to the FOSS community participants and enthusiasts to come together and engage in knowledge sharing activities through technical talks, workshops, panel discussions, hackathons and much more. 2019 was third year of Devconf India. First was along with RootConf and second like the last year was stand alone in the Same venue as of this_.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GCI mentor&#39;s summit @ Google headquarters</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2019/gci_mentors_summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2019/gci_mentors_summit/</guid>
      <description>Context Google Code-in is a contest to introduce pre-university students (ages 13-17) to open source software development. Since 2010, 8,108 students from 107 countries have completed over 40,100 open source tasks Because Google Code-in is often the first experience many students have with open source, the contest is designed to make it easy for students to jump right in. I was one of the mentors in this first time for Fedora program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fedora 30 Release Party Event Report</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2019/fedora_30_release_party/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2019/fedora_30_release_party/</guid>
      <description>Context Celebrating Fedora Release Party is now a custom in Bangalore. This time, although late, we organized it in Red Hat Banglaore Engineering office. We were expecting 30 people to attend the party and we received a fairly good response with ~25 people on and off. Some came for SilverBlue, some to install Fedora 30 and some wanted to know more about the 31 changesets. It was a rather successful event considering it was a working day AND RootConf was at the same $day:time on a different part of city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flock2018</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2018/flock_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2018/flock_blog/</guid>
      <description>WOW! What an experience it was to meet all the people I have been knowing through IRC..faceless people with random nick that has nothing to do with their name.. but brilliant minds who make a very open, inclusive, welcoming and a powerful project possible!
 This was my first Flock and It has been the best conference/event I have ever attended.
 Unlike other conferences where there are a lot of people presenting their own project and are distributed in groups, everyone in the Flock was connected to a single string, Fedora!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>websiteInfo</title>
      <link>https://vipul.dev/2018/websiteinfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://vipul.dev/2018/websiteinfo/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s discuss vsiddhar.me I have been suggested multiple time to manage a blog, share my stories, events and ideas, but as being a &amp;lsquo;Pro&amp;rsquo; procrastinator, I haven&amp;rsquo;t run from my responsibilities and thus, haven&amp;rsquo;t done the right thing! Sadly, this changes now. I have decided to manage this colorless website (Hugo+Coder, as it requires ~no effort). If I am alive and in right sense, I will be putting at least one post every weekmonth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
